<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Apple Hot News</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/hotnews/</link>
<description>Hot News provided by Apple.</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<copyright>Copyright 2016, Apple Inc.</copyright>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 15:53:26 PDT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 15:53:26 PDT</lastBuildDate>
<category>Apple</category>
<generator>In house</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss/</docs><item>
<title>Apple Reports Second Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2016/04/26Apple-Reports-Second-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced financial results for its fiscal 2016 second quarter ended March 26. The company posted quarterly revenue of $50.6 billion and quarterly net income of $10.5 billion, or $1.90 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $58 billion and net income of $13.6 billion, or $2.33 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 39.4 percent compared to 40.8 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 67 percent of the quarter’s revenue. “Our team executed extremely well in the face of strong macroeconomic headwinds,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “We are very happy with the continued strong growth in revenue from Services, thanks to the incredible strength of the Apple ecosystem and our growing base of over 1 billion active devices.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 14:44:21 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Final Cut Pro X helps small company delight world’s biggest clients</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/final-cut-pro/in-action/trim-editing/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>When Trim Editing started creating music videos over a decade ago, just paying the rent was a huge accomplishment. Now, the small East London company is crafting award-winning visuals for big brands — like Audi, Nike, Adidas, and Guinness — propelled by the power of Final Cut Pro X. The video editing software’s comprehensive features allow Trim Editing to organize film and audio clips, pull together compelling projects, and make changes on the fly. “When I’m playing back an edit for a director, they’ll say, ‘Okay, let’s go and make those changes I talked about.’ I’ll say, ‘Oh, no, they’re already done,’ and we’ll jump back and watch it again. People can’t believe that I’ve magically done the change before we even finish playback,” says editor Thomas Grove Carter. </description>
<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 10:05:59 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces 9.7-inch iPad Pro</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad-pro/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today introduced the 9.7-inch iPad Pro, which at just under one pound features a new pro Retina display with greater brightness, wider color gamut, lower reflectivity, Night Shift mode, and new True Tone display technology. The new iPad Pro also has a 64-bit A9X chip that rivals most portable PCs. “iPad Pro is a new generation of iPad that is indispensable and immersive, enabling people to be more productive and more creative. It’s incredibly fast, extremely portable, and completely natural to use with your fingers, Apple Pencil, and Smart Keyboard. And now it comes in two sizes,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 12:00:03 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces iPhone SE — the Most Powerful Phone with a 4-inch Display</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iphone-se/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today introduced iPhone SE, the most powerful phone with a 4-inch display, in a compact aluminum design that has been updated with matte-chamfered edges, a color-matched stainless steel Apple logo, and four metallic finishes. iPhone SE offers the same 64-bit A9 chip offered in iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s. “iPhone SE is packed with a stunning 4-inch Retina display, advanced 64-bit A9 chip with M9 motion co-processor, longer battery life, 12-megapixel iSight camera with True Tone flash, Live Photos, 4K video, faster LTE and Wi-Fi, and Touch ID with Apple Pay. Everyone who wants a smaller phone is going to love iPhone SE,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 11:58:09 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Advances Health Apps with CareKit</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/carekit/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced CareKit, a new software framework designed to help developers enable people to actively manage their own medical conditions. iPhone apps using CareKit make it easier for individuals to keep track of care plans and monitor symptoms and medication, providing insights that help people better understand their own health. “We believe that giving individuals the tools to understand what is happening with their health is incredibly powerful, and apps designed using CareKit make this a reality by empowering people to take a more active role in their care,” said Jeff Williams, Apple’s chief operating officer.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 11:40:55 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces Advancements to ResearchKit</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/researchkit/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple today announced advancements to the open source ResearchKit framework that bring genetic data and a series of medical tests typically conducted in an exam room to iPhone apps. Medical researchers are adopting these new features to design targeted studies for diseases and conditions that affect billions of people and to gather more specific types of data from participants. “The response to ResearchKit has been fantastic. Virtually overnight, many ResearchKit studies became the largest in history and researchers are gaining insights and making discoveries that weren’t possible before,” said Jeff Williams, Apple’s chief operating officer.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2016 11:30:27 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Record First Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2016/01/26Apple-Reports-Record-First-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced financial results for its fiscal 2016 first quarter ended December 26, 2015. The company posted record quarterly revenue of $75.9 billion and record quarterly net income of $18.4 billion, or $3.28 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $74.6 billion and net income of $18 billion, or $3.06 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 40.1 percent compared to 39.9 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 66 percent of the quarter’s revenue. “Our team delivered Apple’s biggest quarter ever, thanks to the world’s most innovative products and all-time record sales of iPhone, Apple Watch, and Apple TV,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “The growth of our Services business accelerated during the quarter to produce record results, and our installed base recently crossed a major milestone of one billion active devices.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 15:05:46 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Record-Breaking Holiday Season for the App Store</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2016/01/06Record-Breaking-Holiday-Season-for-the-App-Store.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Customers around the world made this holiday season the biggest ever for the App Store, setting new records during the weeks of Christmas and New Year’s. In the two weeks ending January 3, customers spent over $1.1 billion on apps and in-app purchases, setting back-to-back weekly records for traffic and purchases. January 1 marked the biggest day in App Store history with customers spending over $144 million. “The App Store had a holiday season for the record books. We are excited that our customers downloaded and enjoyed so many incredible apps for iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch, and Apple TV, spending over $20 billion on the App Store last year alone,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “We’re grateful to all the developers who have created the most innovative and exciting apps in the world for our customers. We can’t wait for what’s to come in 2016.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 15:41:09 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Names Jeff Williams Chief Operating Officer</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/12/17Apple-Names-Jeff-Williams-Chief-Operating-Officer.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced that Jeff Williams has been named chief operating officer and Johny Srouji is joining Apple’s executive team as senior vice president for Hardware Technologies. Phil Schiller, senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing, will expand his role to include leadership of the App Store across all Apple platforms. Apple also announced that Tor Myhren will join Apple in the first calendar quarter of 2016 as vice president of Marketing Communications, reporting to CEO Tim Cook. “We are fortunate to have incredible depth and breadth of talent across Apple’s executive team. As we come to the end of the year, we’re recognizing the contributions already being made by two key executives,” said Cook. “Jeff is hands-down the best operations executive I’ve ever worked with, and Johny’s team delivers world-class silicon designs which enable new innovations in our products year after year.”</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 13:49:47 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Record Fourth Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/10/27Apple-Reports-Record-Fourth-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced financial results for its fiscal 2015 fourth quarter ended September 26. The company posted quarterly revenue of $51.5 billion and quarterly net profit of $11.1 billion, or $1.96 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $42.1 billion and net profit of $8.5 billion, or $1.42 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 39.9 percent compared to 38 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 62 percent of the quarter’s revenue. The growth was fueled by record fourth quarter sales of iPhone, the expanded availability of Apple Watch, and all-time records for Mac sales and revenue from services. “Fiscal 2015 was Apple’s most successful year ever, with revenue growing 28 percent to nearly $234 billion. This continued success is the result of our commitment to making the best, most innovative products on earth, and it’s a testament to the tremendous execution by our teams,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “We are heading into the holidays with our strongest product lineup yet, including iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus, Apple Watch with an expanded lineup of cases and bands, the new iPad Pro, and the all-new Apple TV which begins shipping this week.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 13:55:18 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Updates iMac Family with Stunning New Retina Displays</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/imac/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has updated the entire iMac family, bringing a new Retina 4K display to the 21.5-inch iMac for the first time and the Retina 5K display to every 27-inch iMac. The updated iMacs also feature more powerful processors and graphics, two Thunderbolt 2 ports, and new storage options that make the high-performance Fusion Drive even more affordable. Apple also introduced a new lineup of wireless accessories including the all-new Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse 2, and Magic Trackpad 2. “From the first iMac to today, the spirit of iMac has never wavered — deliver the ultimate desktop experience with the latest technologies, gorgeous displays, and cutting-edge designs,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “These are the most stunning iMacs we’ve ever made. With our gorgeous new Retina displays, more powerful processors and graphics, and all-new Magic accessories, the new iMac continues to redefine the ultimate desktop experience.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 11:12:45 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>OS X El Capitan Available as Free Update Tomorrow</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/09/29OS-X-El-Capitan-Available-as-a-Free-Update-Tomorrow.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>OS X El Capitan, the latest major release of the world’s most advanced desktop operating system, will be available Wednesday, September 30, as a free update for Mac users. El Capitan builds on the groundbreaking features and beautiful design of OS X Yosemite. “People love using their Macs, and one of the biggest reasons is the power and ease of use of OS X,” said Craig Federighi, Apple’s senior vice president of Software Engineering. “El Capitan refines the Mac experience and improves performance in a lot of little ways that make a very big difference. Feedback from our OS X beta program has been incredibly positive and we think customers are going to love their Macs even more with El Capitan.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 14:03:20 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Announces Record iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus Sales</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/09/28Apple-Announces-Record-iPhone-6s-iPhone-6s-Plus-Sales.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced it has sold more than 13 million new iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus models, a new record, just three days after launch. iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus will be available in more than 40 additional countries beginning October 9 including Italy, Mexico, Russia, Spain, and Taiwan. The new iPhones will be available in over 130 countries by the end of the year. “Sales for iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus have been phenomenal, blowing past any previous first weekend sales results in Apple’s history,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “Customers’ feedback is incredible and they are loving 3D Touch and Live Photos, and we can’t wait to bring iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus to customers in even more countries on October 9.”</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2015 14:37:05 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/iphone-6s/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus, adding a powerful new dimension to iPhone’s revolutionary Multi-Touch interface. The new iPhones introduce 3D Touch, which enables intuitive new ways to access features and interact with content. iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus feature Retina HD displays made from the strongest glass on any smartphone and 7000 series aluminum, the same alloy used in the aerospace industry, in metallic finishes that now include rose gold. The new iPhones also introduce a transformative new approach to photography called Live Photos, bringing still images to life by capturing a moment in motion. “The only thing that has changed with iPhone 6s and iPhone 6s Plus is everything — 3D Touch lets users interact with iPhone in entirely new and fun ways, and the innovative Live Photos brings your pictures to life,” said Philip Schiller, Apple’s senior vice president of Worldwide Marketing. “These are the most advanced iPhones ever, with 7000 series aluminum, ion-strengthened glass, the new 64-bit A9 chip, 12-megapixel iSight and 5-megapixel FaceTime HD cameras, faster Touch ID, LTE, and Wi-Fi. Customers are going to love them.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:34:17 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Brings Innovation Back to Television with All-New Apple TV</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/tv/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced the all-new Apple TV, bringing a revolutionary experience to the living room based on apps built for the television. Apps on Apple TV let you choose what to watch and when you watch it. And with the new Siri Remote, you can search with your voice for TV shows and movies across multiple content providers simultaneously. Apple TV runs the all-new tvOS operating system, based on Apple’s iOS, enabling iOS developers to create new apps and games specifically for Apple TV and deliver them directly to users through the new Apple TV App Store. “There has been so much innovation in entertainment and programming through iOS apps, we want to bring that same excitement to the television,” said Eddy Cue, Apple’s senior vice president of Internet Software and Services. “Apps make the TV experience even more compelling for viewers and we think apps represent the future of TV.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:33:16 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces iPad Pro Featuring Epic 12.9-inch Retina Display</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ipad-pro/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has introduced the all-new iPad Pro, featuring a 12.9-inch Retina display with 5.6 million pixels and the new 64-bit A9X chip. The new larger iPad Pro is thin and light and provides all-day battery life. Apple also introduced Apple Pencil for iPad Pro and the new Smart Keyboard, available for purchase separately. “iPad Pro is the most advanced and powerful iPad we have ever made. Its beautiful and large 12.9-inch Retina display has 5.6 million pixels and provides an immersive experience for content and apps. The iPad Pro is far and away the fastest iOS device we have ever made — its A9X chip beats most portable PCs in both CPU and graphics tasks, but is thin and light enough to hold all day,” said Apple’s Philip Schiller. “The innovative Apple Pencil and new Smart Keyboard enable users to customize their iPad Pro experience to the particular apps they use and the work they do, making iPad Pro ideal for everything from professional productivity to advanced 3D design.”</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:32:27 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Introduces watchOS 2 with Native Apps and New Apple Watch Sport Models</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/watch/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has introduced new Apple Watch cases and bands, available starting today, including new gold and rose gold aluminum Apple Watch Sport models. watchOS 2 — which arrives as a free update on September 16 — makes apps faster and more fluid by running natively on Apple Watch, and introduces new watch faces, the ability for third-party apps to display information on the watch face as complications, and an innovative way to see future events, past headlines, and more with Time Travel. Apple Watch collections are expanding with new case colors and fresh new bands. With new standalone Sport Bands that range from rich vibrant colors to more neutral tones, Apple Watch is now more customizable than ever.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:15:22 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple and Hermès Unveil the Apple Watch Hermès Collection</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/apple-watch-hermes/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple and Hermès have introduced Apple Watch Hermès, a new collection of Apple Watch in stainless steel with finely crafted leather bands in distinctive styles from Hermès, including the Single Tour, Double Tour, and Cuff, while respecting the design and functionality of the Apple Watch. The collaboration merges Apple’s unparalleled product innovation with the heritage, iconography, and craftsmanship of Hermès, creating a unique expression of Apple Watch. “Apple and Hermès make very different products, but they reflect the deep appreciation of quality design,” said Jonathan Ive, Apple’s chief design officer. “Both companies are motivated by a sincere pursuit of excellence and the desire to create something that is not compromised. Apple Watch Hermès is a true testament to that belief.”
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:14:19 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>iOS 9 Available as a Free Update for iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch Users September 16</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/ios/?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple announced that iOS 9 will be available on September 16 as a free update for iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch users. iOS 9 makes iOS devices more intelligent and proactive with powerful search and improved Siri features, all while protecting users’ privacy. The way you interact with iPad gets even better with iOS 9, thanks to new multitasking features that let users view and interact with two apps at once, side by side. “iOS 9 is packed with intelligence that makes every experience with iPhone and iPad even more powerful — Siri can do more than ever and new proactive assistance helps you get more done before you ask, all while protecting users’ privacy,” said Craig Federighi, Apple’s senior vice president of Software Engineering.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 14:13:21 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apple Reports Record Third Quarter Results</title>
<link>http://www.apple.com/pr/library/2015/07/21Apple-Reports-Record-Third-Quarter-Results.html?sr=hotnews.rss</link>
<description>Apple has announced financial results for its fiscal 2015 third quarter ended June 27. The company posted quarterly revenue of $49.6 billion and quarterly net profit of $10.7 billion, or $1.85 per diluted share. These results compare to revenue of $37.4 billion and net profit of $7.7 billion, or $1.28 per diluted share, in the year-ago quarter. Gross margin was 39.7 percent compared to 39.4 percent in the year-ago quarter. International sales accounted for 64 percent of the quarter’s revenue. The growth was fueled by record third-quarter sales of iPhone and Mac, all-time record revenue from services, and the successful launch of Apple Watch. “We had an amazing quarter, with iPhone revenue up 59 percent over last year, strong sales of Mac, all-time record revenue from services, driven by the App Store, and a great start for Apple Watch,” said Tim Cook, Apple’s CEO. “The excitement for Apple Music has been incredible, and we’re looking forward to releasing iOS 9, OS X El Capitan, and watchOS 2 to customers in the fall.”</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 14:29:30 PDT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>